A Guide to the Plats and certificates of the Virginia Land Office, 1779-1982
Library of Virginia
- 1799
  - Per-Pet, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Ph-Po, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Pr-Pu, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Puckett, George, 1799. (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Ra, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Ree, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Rei-Rey, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Ri, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Rob, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Rod-Row, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Roots, Thomas R., 1799. (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Ru, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Sa-Se, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Sha-She, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Shi-Shu, 1799. (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Si-Sk, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Benjamin - Smith, Henry, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Isaac - Smith, Obediah, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Richard - Smith, William, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Sn-Sp, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Sta-Ste, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Sti-Sto, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Stu-Sw, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Ta, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Te, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Th, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Ti-To, 1799. (Box 181, Folder 13)
  - Tr-Ty, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - V, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Wad-Wag, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Wal, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Wam-Wat, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Web-Wel, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Wes-Wh, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Wi, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Williams, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Willson-Wilson, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Wo-Wy, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Wood-Woods, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - Y, 1799. (Box 182, Folder 13)
- 1800
  - Ad-Ah, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Al, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - An, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Ar, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - As-Ay, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Bai-Bal, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Ban-Barn, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Barr-Bay, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Be, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Bi-Bl, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Boa-Book, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Boon-Boy, 1800. (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Bra-Bri, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Bro, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Bru-Bry, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Buc-Burnley, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Burns-By, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Cab-Cal, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Campbell, A., 1800. (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Campbell, D.-W., 1800. (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Can-Carn, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Carr-Ce, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Ch, 1800. (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - Cla-Clel, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Clem-Clo, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Cob-Cole, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Coll-Con, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Coo-Cop, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Cor-Coy, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Crab-Cran, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Craw-Croo, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Cu, 1800. (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Dab-Davis, J., 1800. (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Davis, J.-Davison, H., 1800. (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Davison, H.-Day, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - De, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Di, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Doa-Donally, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Donnell-Dow, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Dr-Du, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Ea-En, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Er-Es, 1800. (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - Ev-Ew, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Fa-Fe, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Fi, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Fl, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Fo, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Forde, Standish, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Forde, Standish, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Fra-Frog, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Fros-Fry, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Fulkerson, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Fu, 1800. (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - Ga-Ge, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Gi-Gl, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Go, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Gr, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Gw, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Hac-Hal, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Ham-Han, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Har-Harr, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Hars-Hay, 1800. (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Hea-Hend, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Henk-Hew, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Hic-Hig, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Hill-Hit, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Hob-Hop, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Hor-Hox, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Hud-Hull, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Huk-Hut, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - I, 1800. (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Jac-James, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Jameson-Jet, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Jo-Ju, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Ke, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Kid-Kind, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - King, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Kingan-Ky, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Laid-Lain, 1800. (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Lam-Lay, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Lea-Lee, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Leg-Ley, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Li, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Lo, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Lu, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - McCauley-McCoy, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - McCraw-McDougall, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - McFarland-McKinzee, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - McLoughlin-McVey, 1800. (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Mad-Maj, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Mal-Mar, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Mas-Maz, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Me, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Mi, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Mof-Moro, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Morr-Moy, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Mu, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - N, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - O, 1800. (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Pa, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Pe, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Pearis, George, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Ph-Pl, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Po, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Pra-Pri, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Preston, Francis-John, 1800. (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Preston, Robert (Lee County), 1800. (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Preston, Robert (Russell County), 1800. (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Preston, Robert (Washington County), 1800. (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Preston, W., 1800. (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Ra-Reed, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Reid-Rey, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Rh-Ri, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Roa-Rob, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Rod-Roy, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Ru-Ry, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Sa-Se, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Sha, 1800. (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - She-Shu, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Si, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Sk-Sl, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Aaron-Jarvis, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Smith, John, - Sn, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - So-Sp, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Sta, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Ste-Sti, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Sto-Stu, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Su-Sw, 1800. (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Ta, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Te, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Th-Ti, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - To-Tu, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - U, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - V, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Wad-Wam, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - War-We, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Wh-Williams, 1800. (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Willibough-Wiz, 1800. (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Wo-Wy, 1800. (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Y-Z, 1800. (Box 197, Folder 3)
- 1801
  - Ab-Ad, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Ak-Al, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - An, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Ar, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Arnold, George, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Arbuckle, Mathew, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - As-Av, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Bac-Bak, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Bal-Ban, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Bar-Bay, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Bea, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Bel-Bi, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - Bl, 1801. (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Bog-Bor, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Bra-Bre, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Bou-Boy, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Bro, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Bru-Bry, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Buc-Bur, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Bus-By, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Cab-Cal, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Cam-Cap, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Car-Cav, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Ce-Ch, 1801. (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - Cl, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Cob-Col, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Com-Coo, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Cop-Coy, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Cr-Cu, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Craig, Hiram; Fulkerson, Peter; McCormack, John; Legget, Robert, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Crawford, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Da, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - De-Di, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Do, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Dr-Du, 1801. (Box 200, Folder 11)
  - Ea, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Ed-Es, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Ev-Ey, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Fa-Fi, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Fl-Fr, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Fu, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Ga-Ge, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Gi, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Go-Gra, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Gre-Gw, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Hac-Han, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Hairston, 1801. (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Hall, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Harb-Harn, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Harr-Hart, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Hat-Hay, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - He, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Hi, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Ho, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Hu-Hy, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - I, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Ja-Je, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Jackson, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - Jo, 1801. (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Jones, 1801. (Box 202)
  - Ka-Ke, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Ki-Ko, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - King, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - La, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Le, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Li, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Lo, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Lu-Ly, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 0)
  - McCa-McCl, 1801. (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - McCo-McG, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - McK-McW, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Mac-Man, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Mar-Mas, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Mat-May, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Me-Mi, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Miller, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Mo, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Mu, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - N, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - O, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Pan-Par, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - Pat, 1801. (Box 204, Folder 13)
  - Pe, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Ph-Pi, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Po-Pr, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Preston, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Q, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Ra, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Rea-Ren, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Rey-Ri, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Ro, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Robertson, Henry, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Ru-Ry, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - Sa, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - Sc-Se, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - Sha-She, 1801. (Box 205, Folder 15)
  - Shi, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Sho-Si, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Sk-Sl, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Smith/Smyth, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Sn-Sp, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Sta-Ste, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Sto-Stu, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Su-Sy, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Ta, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Te-Th, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Tr-Ty, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - V, 1801. (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Wa, 1801. (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - We-Wi, 1801. (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Willson/Wilson, 1801. (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Wo-Wy, 1801. (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Y, 1801. (Box 207, Folder 5)
- 1802
  - A, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Bag-Ban, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Bar-Bay, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Be, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Bi-Bl, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Bo, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Bra-Brot, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Brou-Bru, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Bu, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - Buck, Cornelius, 1802. (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Ca-Ce, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Ch-Cl, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Coc-Col, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Con-Cow, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Crab-Crai, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Cr, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Cu, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Da-De, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Di, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Do-Du, 1802. (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - E, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Fa-Fl, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Fo-Fu, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Ga-Ge, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Gi-Go, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Gra-Gre, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Gri-Gu, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Hai-Ham, 1802. (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Han, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Har, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Hau-Hay, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - He, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Hi, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Ho, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Hu-Hy, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - I, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - J, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Ka-Ke, 1802. (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Ki-Ko, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - La-Le, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Li-Ly, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - McCa-McCl, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - McCo-McCu, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - McD, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - McG-McR, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - Ma-Me, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Mi, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Mo-Mu, 1802. (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - N, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - O, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - Pac-Patr, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - Patt-Pay, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Pe, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Pi-Po, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Pr, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - Q, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Ra-Re, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - Rh-Ri, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - R0-Ru, 1802. (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - Sa-Se, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Sh-Sl, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Sm, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Sn-Sp, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Sta-Ste, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Sti-Sw, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Ta-Te, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Th-Ti, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - To, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - Tr-Ty, 1802. (Box 214, Folder 10)
  - V, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Wad-Wam, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - War-Way, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - We, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Wh, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Wic-Wills, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Willson-Wis, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - Wo, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - Wr-Wy, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - Y, 1802. (Box 215, Folder 10)
- 1803
  - A, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Bai-Bak, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - Bal-Be, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Bi-Bo, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Br, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Bu, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - Cab-Cal, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Cam-Carr, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Cars-Ce, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Ch, 1803. (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Cl, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Co, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Cr-Cu, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Da-De, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Di-Dy, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - E, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Fa-Fi, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Fl-Fu, 1803. (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Ga-Gl, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Go, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Gr-Gw, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Hai-Harl, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Harm-Haw, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - He, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Hi, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - Hog-Hor, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Hos-Hoy, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - Hu-Hy, 1803. (Box 218, Folder 10)
  - I, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - J, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Ke-Kin, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Kin-Kir, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - La-Le, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Li, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Lo-Lu, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - McA-McC, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - McF-McP, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Mad-Mar, 1803. (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Mat-Maz, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Me, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Mi, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Mo, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Mu-My, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - N, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - O, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Pa, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Pe-Ph, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Pi-Pu, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Q, 1803. (Box 220, Folder 11)
  - Ra-Re, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Ri-Rob, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Rod-Ru, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Se, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Sh, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Sk-Sl, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Sm, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - Sn-Sp, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 8)
  - Sta-Ste, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 9)
  - Sti-Str, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - Su-Sw, 1803. (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - Ta, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Th-Ti, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - To-Tu, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 3)
  - U, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - V, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - Wad-Wal, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - Wam-We, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - Wik-Will, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - Wilson, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 9)
  - Wim-Wit, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 10)
  - Wo, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 11)
  - Wr-Wy, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 12)
  - Y, 1803. (Box 222, Folder 13)
- 1804
  - A-Cl, 1804. (Box 223)
  - Co-E, 1804. (Box 224)
  - F-Ho, 1804. (Box 225)
  - Hu-L, 1804. (Box 226)
  - M-Pee, 1804. (Box 227)
  - Pen-Sl, 1804. (Box 228)
  - Sm-We, 1804. (Box 229)
  - Wh-Z, 1804. (Box 230)
- 1805
  - A-B, 1805. (Box 231)
  - C-El, 1805. (Box 232)
  - Er-Ha, 1805. (Box 233)
  - He-K, 1805. (Box 234)
  - L-M, 1805. (Box 235)
  - N-Re, 1805. (Box 236)
  - Ri-S, 1805. (Box 237)
  - T-Z, 1805. (Box 238)
- 1806
  - A-E, 1806. (Box 239)
  - F-L, 1806. (Box 240)
  - M-R, 1806. (Box 241)
  - S-Y, 1806. (Box 242)
- 1807
  - A-G, 1807. (Box 243)
  - H-R, 1807. (Box 244)
  - S-Y, 1807. (Box 245)
- 1808
  - A-Cl, 1808. (Box 246)
  - Co-G, 1808. (Box 247)
  - H-K, 1808. (Box 248)
  - L-Pi, 1808. (Box 249)
  - Po-Ste, 1808. (Box 250)
  - Sta-Y, 1808. (Box 251)
- 1809
  - A-Bri, 1809. (Box 252)
  - Bro-Cre, 1809. (Box 253)
  - Cro-E, 1809. (Box 254)
  - F-Hal, 1809. (Box 255)
  - Ham-Hu, 1809. (Box 256)
  - I-L, 1809. (Box 257)
  - M, 1809. (Box 258)
  - N-Robe, 1809. (Box 259)
  - Robi-Ste, 1809. (Box 260)
  - Sto-We, 1809. (Box 261)
  - Wh-Z, 1809. (Box 262)
- 1810
  - A-Ca, 1810. (Box 263)
  - Ch-D, 1810. (Box 264)
  - E-G, 1810. (Box 265)
  - H-Ke, 1810. (Box 266)
  - Ki-Mi, 1810. (Box 267)
  - Mo-Re, 1810. (Box 268)
  - Ri-S, 1810. (Box 269)
  - T-Z, 1810. (Box 270)
- 1811
  - A-C, 1811. (Box 271)
  - D-H, 1811. (Box 272)
  - I-Q, 1811. (Box 273)
  - R-T, 1811. (Box 274)
  - U-Y, 1811. (Box 275)
- 1812
  - A-Cl, 1812. (Box 276)
  - Co-Ha, 1812. (Box 277)
  - He-Mc, 1812. (Box 278)
  - Ma-Ri, 1812. (Box 279)
  - Ro-We, 1812. (Box 280)
  - Wh-Z, 1812. (Box 281)
- 1813
  - A-F, 1813. (Box 282)
  - G-K, 1813. (Box 283)
  - L-R, 1813. (Box 284)
  - S-Y, 1813. (Box 285)
- 1814
  - A-He, 1814. (Box 286)
  - Ho-T, 1814. (Box 287)
  - W-Y, 1814. (Box 288)
- 1815
  - A-C, 1815. (Box 289)
  - D-Han, 1815. (Box 290)
  - Har-L, 1815. (Box 291)
  - M-Q, 1815. (Box 292)
  - R-V, 1815. (Box 293)
  - W-Z, 1815. (Box 294)
- 1816
  - A-C, 1816. (Box 295)
  - D-He, 1816. (Box 296)
  - Hi_Mi, 1816. (Box 297)
  - Mo-Sr, 1816. (Box 298)
  - St-Y, 1816. (Box 299)
- 1817
  - A-D, 1817. (Box 300)
  - E-Le, 1817. (Box 301)
  - Li-R, 1817. (Box 302)
  - S-Y, 1817. (Box 303)
- 1818
  - A-Ca, 1818. (Box 304)
  - Ch-Fl, 1818. (Box 305)
  - Fo-H, 1818. (Box 306)
  - I-Ma, 1818. (Box 307)
  - Me-R, 1818. (Box 308)
  - S-Wh, 1818. (Box 309)
  - Wi-Y, 1818. (Box 310)
- 1819
  - A-C, 1819. (Box 311)
  - D-He, 1819. (Box 312)
  - Hi-Mi, 1819. (Box 313)
  - Mo-Sm, 1819. (Box 314)
  - Sn-Y, 1819. (Box 315)
- 1820
  - A-Co, 1820. (Box 316)
  - Cr-G, 1820. (Box 317)
  - H-K, 1820. (Box 318)
  - L-P, 1820. (Box 319)
  - R-We, 1820. (Box 320)
  - Wh-Z, 1820. (Box 321)
- 1821
  - A-E, 1821. (Box 322)
  - F-L, 1821. (Box 323)
  - M-Si, 1821. (Box 324)
  - Sk-Y, 1821. (Box 325)
- 1822
  - A-Di, 1822. (Box 326)
  - Do-H, 1822. (Box 327)
  - J-Pl, 1822. (Box 328)
  - Po-V, 1822. (Box 329)
  - W-Y, 1822. (Box 330)